Shine brighter. Shine farther.
Life-Size 2 is a family, fantasy film directed by Steven K. Tsuchida.
Grace Manning is in the middle of her quarter-life crisis,
realizing she is in over her head as CEO.
To make matters worse, her wild-child ways are
causing the company’s stock to plummet.
With the help of her young next-door neighbor, Grace’s old Eve doll magically awakens to help get Grace
back on track and give her the confidence to be the woman and leader Eve knows Grace can be.
Eve, played by Tyra Banks.
Grace Martin, played by Francia Raísa.
Calum, played by Gavin Stenhouse.
Brendan Butler, played by Hank Chen.
Lex, played by Alison Fernández.
Tahlia, played by Shanica Knowles.
Life-Size 2, also known as Life-Size 2: A Christmas Eve, is a 2018 American fantasy-comedy
television film directed by Steven Tsuchida and starring Tyra Banks and Francia Raisa.
It is the sequel to Life-Size starring Banks and Lindsay Lohan, which originally
premiered in 2000 on ABC as part of The Wonderful World of Disney.
The sequel was produced by Banks, Stephanie Allain, Roger M.
Bobb, and Angi Bones.
It premiered during Freeform's 25 Days of Christmas, on December 2, 2018.
In February 2020, Banks revealed she was working on Life-Size 3.